{
    "subject": "resource/Ella_Fitzgerald's_Christmas",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Dave_Dexter,_Jr.",
    "human_readable": "Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas was produced by Dave Dexter, Jr.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8509542942047119,
            "question": "Who produced Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7474044561386108,
            "question": "What year was Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7439174652099609,
            "question": "Was Dave Dexter, Jr. involved in music production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5637254118919373,
            "question": "Is Dave Dexter, Jr. known for producing other types of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5187702775001526,
            "question": "What is the name of Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4366218149662018,
            "question": "What makes Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album special or memorable?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38961952924728394,
            "question": "What genre is Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3394433557987213,
            "question": "Are there any unique features or themes in Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31412243843078613,
            "question": "Does Ella Fitzgerald have other albums besides her Christmas album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17993392050266266,
            "question": "Are there any other famous musicians who have released Christmas albums?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas was produced by Dave Dexter, Jr.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2188_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Ella Fitzgerald have other albums besides her Christmas album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2188_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any unique features or themes in Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2188_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2188_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2188_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe information in the documents does not support this triple. In fact, one of the documents mentions \"More info / Album review / Recorded in 1967 and originally released that same year by Capitol Records as an LP (and re-released seasonally several times since then), Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas is a rarity among rarities in that it is a holiday album that actually holds up as a mature artistic statement.\" which implies that the producer was not mentioned, but also there is no mention of Dave Dexter, Jr. being involved with Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention anything about Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album being produced by Dave Dexter, Jr. Instead, the documents discuss Frank DeVol as an arranger and provide information on how Ella Fitzgerald interpreted and performed various holiday standards in her 1960s albums."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no evidence or information provided to suggest that Dave Dexter, Jr. produced Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album. The information given indicates that the album was arranged by Frank DeVol and released by Capitol Records.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "None of the provided text mentions Dave Dexter, Jr. as a producer for Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Dave Dexter, Jr. as the producer of Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas, but instead mentions Frank DeVol as the arranger and composer.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Dave Dexter, Jr. as the producer of \"Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas.\" Instead, it highlights Frank DeVol as the arranger who provides the perfect backdrop to Ella's vocals, indicating that Frank DeVol, not Dave Dexter, Jr., was involved in the production and arrangement of the album.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}